Guide to the Lucy Kramer Cohen Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- June 2014 Acquisition, circa 1900-2003; 8.54; (13 boxes) + 7 record albums
  - Photographs, 1930s-1980s, undated
    - Family, travel, and Indian Affairs photographs, 1930s-1980s (Box 47)
    - Portraits, undated (Box 48)
  - Audiovisual materials, 1953-1955
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Felix Cohen film, undated, 1953-1955 (Box 49)
    - Funeral of Felix Cohen, original (1 of 3), 1953 October 21; 1; 00:21:52; There is a high amount of hum on the recording. (Box 49, Item barcode 39002091399718)
      Taken from Danzansky Funeral Parlor, public address system. Beginning: music only. Complete recording to be made for Lucy Cohen.
    - Funeral of Felix Cohen, original (2 of 3), 1953 October 21; 1; 00:30:17; There is static and a high amount of hum on the tape. There is also high background noise on the recording. The program is distorted at times. There is a squeal in the audio at 25:43 until the end. (Box 49, Item barcode 39002091399726)
      Taken from Danzansky Funeral Home, public address system.
    - Funeral of Felix Cohen, original (3 of 3), 1953 October 21; 1; 00:10:35 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002091399734)
    - CCNY Presentation of Felix S. Cohen Portrait, 1954 November 15; 1; 00:30:56; The program begins and ends abruptly. There is high background noise on the recording. The program is distorted at times. (Box 49, Item barcode 39002091399742)
      Prof. Daniel J. Bronstein, Head of the Philosophy Dept. presiding. Joel David Wolf[sahm] making presnetation of FSC fund and Oscar L. Chapman, chair of fund. President Buell Gallagher, CCNY, receiving the portrait for the college.
    - Audiodisc, Felix S. Cohen Memorial Service, 1953 October 21 (Box 50 (Record album storage))
    - Audiodisc, Felix S. Cohen Memorial Service, 1953 October 21 (Box 51 (Record album storage))
    - Audiodisc, Felix S. Cohen Memorial Service, 1953 December 4 (Box 52 (Record album storage))
    - Audiodisc, Felix S. Cohen Memorial Service, 1953 October 21 (Box 53 (Record album storage))
    - Audiodisc, Felix S. Cohen Memorial Service, 1953 October 21 (Box 54 (Record album storage))
    - Audiodisc, Felix S. Cohen Memorial Service, 1953 October 21 (Box 55 (Record album storage))
    - Audiodisc, Felix S. Cohen Memorial Service, 1953 October 21 (Box 56 (Record album storage))